Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 29 (Box 4, Folder 70-73)
    - Berkeley Evening School / Telfer 1965
    - Berkeley University Teachers Union / 03/45/65
    - Berkeley University Teachers Union / Smale nd 2pp
    - California Monthly / February 1965
    - Call to a faculty meeting / Krech 09/22/65
    - Call to a meeting Free Speech Movement / nd
    - Call to a meeting. GCC / nd 2pp
    - Call to an open meeting / 03/24/65
    - CNVA West and War Resisters League / 03/23/65
    - Committee on Academic Freedom / nd
    - Faculty Peace Committee / nd 2pp
    - Faculty Peace Committee / Wilson nd
    - Free Student Union / 05/05/65
    - Free Student Union / 05/10/65
    - Free Student Union / 05/10/65
    - Free Student Union / 05/15/65
    - Free University / 04/05/65
    - Free Speech Movement / 03/19/65
    - Free Speech Movement Defense Fund / Stein 08/10/65
    - Free Speech Movement Steering Committee / nd 2cc
    - Invitation to rally / nd
    - Iranian Students Association / 05/13/65
    - Iranian Students Association / nd
    - Leaflet / Helson 08/06/65
    - Leaflet for anti-war rally / 04/17/65
    - Leaflet. Rally for civil rights / 03/12/65
    - Letter / Lepawsky 01/02/65 2pp
    - Letter / Louisell 09/15/65
    - Letter / Malia 09/09/65 5pp
    - Letter. UC Faculty members / 04/21/65
    - Letter. UC Faculty members / 10/11/65
    - Letter. UC Faculty members / nd
    - Memo / Malia 01/29/65
    - Memo / May 03/04/65 2pp
    - Minutes. Faculty Peace Committee / 10/04/65
    - Note / Barnes 03/23/65
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 09/03/65 12pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 09/30/65
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 10/04/65
    - Office of the Chancellor / Myerson 03/22/65 2pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Myerson 03/31/65 6pp
    - Pamphlet. The Free Society / Goldwater December 1965
    - Peace and Freedom Movement / Littlefield nd
    - Platform. Peace and Freedom Party / nd
    - Proposal. Academic Senate / 01/12/65
    - Report. Academic Senate / 04/4/66 9pp
    - Report. NAACP Legal Defense Fund / October 1965
    - Science. Reprint / 07/23/65
    - Society for Social Responsibility in Science / December 1965 17pp
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / 01/19/65 5pp
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Myerson 07/30/65
    - Student Non-violent Coordinating Committee / nd
    - Telegrams. Reprint. 03/09/65
    - The American Scholar. Reprint / Summer 1965
    - The Defender / 05/09/65 2cc
    - The Defender / 05/23/65
    - The Defender / 05/30/65 5pp
    - The Liberal Democrat / January 1965
    - The Trial. Free Student Union 07/19/65
    - Tract / Anonymous nd
    - UC Faculty members / 01/12/65
    - UC Faculty members / 02/02/65 15pp
    - UC History Department / nd
    - UCLA Alumni Association / 01/13/65
    - Undergraduate Association / 01/11/65
    - University Bulletin / 01/04/65
    - University Bulletin / 01/11/65
    - University Bulletin / 02/01/65
    - University Bulletin / 02/08/65
    - University Bulletin / 03/08/65
    - University Bulletin / 03/15/65
    - University Bulletin / 03/22/65
    - University Bulletin / 04/05/65
    - University Bulletin / 04/19/65
    - University Bulletin / 04/26/65
    - University Bulletin / 05/03/65
    - University Bulletin / 05/10/65
    - University Bulletin / 06/07/65
    - University Bulletin / 06/29/65
    - University Bulletin / 08/16/65
    - University Bulletin / 08/30/65
    - University Bulletin / 09/29/65
    - University Bulletin supplement / 03/08/65
    - Vietnam Day Committee / 09/13/65 9pp
    - War Resisters League / 12/19/65
  - File 30 (Box 4, Folder 74-76)
    - Academic Senate Berkeley Division / 05/17/66
    - Academic Senate Berkeley Division / 05/22/66
    - Academic Senate. Notice of Meeting / 04/10/67
    - ACLU 46th Annual Report / 1967
    - Amnesty International / Summer 1967
    - ASUC Committee / 03/21/66 9pp
    - Bay Area Sparticist League / docketed 03/31/67 2cc
    - Beilenson for Senate / docketed 06/03/68
    - Berkeley Daily Gazette. Reprint / 05/24/66
    - Campaign leaflet. CNP / docketed 03/31/67 2cc
    - Campus Draft Opposition / docketed 05/16/68
    - Campus Friends of Stop the Draft / docketed 04/09/68
    - Campus Mobilization Committee / docketed 04/03/67
    - Catholic Student Organization / 02/17/66
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions / OConnor 08/27/67
    - Christian World Liberation Front / docketed 10/28/69
    - Committee for Academic Freedom / 08/29/67
    - Committee for Departmental Organizations docketed 01/18/67
    - Emergency Committee for Vietnamese Relief / February 1966
    - Essay / Schlesinger 05/04/68
    - Essay / Schurmann 12/03/66 3pp
    - Faculty Peace Committee / 02/21/66
    - Form letter / Martin Luther King, Jr. June 1967
    - Friends World College Headquarters / 06/17/66
    - Funds for Justice / 07/21/66
    - Goodlett for Governor / Casady 05/16/66
    - Heads Up / January 1966
    - IFC and ASUC / docketed 04/03/67
    - Independent Socialist Club / docketed 01/09/67
    - Independent Socialist Club / docketed 04/03/67
    - Invitation to a rally / docketed 07/04/68
    - Leaflet / docketed 03/31/67
    - Leaflet The Public Affairs Bureau of The Sun Reporter / 02/14/66
    - Leaflet. Peace and Freedom Forum / nd
    - Leaflet. RSU / 06/05/69
    - Leaflet. The Strike Committee / 12/06/66
    - Letter / Berreman 03/30/66 2pp
    - Letter / Chamberlain 01/24/67
    - Letter / Diamond 12/08/66
    - Letter / Diamond 12/14/66
    - Letter / Jenner 006/15/66
    - Letter / Jenner 03/01/66
    - Letter / Jenner 03/01/66
    - Letter / Jenner 11/22/67
    - Letter / Lima 06/18/67
    - Letter / Morse 06/13/66
    - Letter / Parker 10/27/68
    - Letter / Schurmann 05/11/66 2pp
    - Letter / White 06/14/66
    - Letter and petition / White 03/15/66
    - Letter. Berreman 05/05/66
    - Letter. War Resisters League of Northern California / 02/02/66
    - Letters to the editor / Balabanian 1966 3pp
    - Memo / Barton 06/09/69
    - Memo / Bouwsma 12/05/66
    - Motion. Academic Senate Berkeley Division / 05/22/66
    - National Farm Workers Association / Chatfield 05/18/66
    - National Farm Workers Association / nd
    - News articles and petition. Reprint. 04/18/77 10pp stapled
    - Newspaper. Young Socialists Alliance / docketed 03/31/67
    - Office of the Chancellor / Cheit 03/21/66
    - Office of the Chancellor / Cheit 11/30/66 2pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Connick 12/07/66
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 02/07/66
    - On Academic Freedom / Coombs Autumn 1967/
    - Pamphlet. Berkeley Citizens Witness for Peace in Vietnam / nd
    - Pamphlet. The Strike Committee / docketed 5 December
    - Peace and Freedom Movement of Alameda County / 04/01/68
    - Petition / Malia 04/11/66
    - Petition in support of Prof. Stamler/ nd
    - Radical Student Union / nd
    - Raymond Tiernan Defense Fund / Stein and Mullins 01/24/66
    - Resolution. Academic Senate / 01/24/67 2pp
    - Resolution. Academic Senate / 01/24/67 2pp 2cc
    - Resolution. Peace and Freedom Party / 10/18/67 2cc
    - Stamler Legal Aid Fund / 07/27/68
    - Stamler Legal Aid Fund / White 11/27/67
    - Statement. Mathematics and statistics faculty members / 12/02/66 3cc
    - Statement. Office of Public Information / 10/23/68
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 12/05/66
    - Telegraph Avenue Liberation Front Manual / 09/19/69
    - The Cycle of Silence / Vol. 26, #1 September 1966
    - The Daily Californian / 09/01/67
    - The Gate / 01/04/65
    - The Gate / 01/11/65
    - The New Leader / 09/29/66
    - The New York Post. Reprint of an editorial / 07/20/67
    - The New York Review. Reprint. / Friedenberg 03/03/66
    - The New York Times. Reprint / 02/08/66
    - Tract. Friends of Ronald Reagan / Jan-Feb 1966
    - TWLF / nd
    - UC Academic Senate. Minutes of the Berkeley Division / 04/25/66
    - United Committee Against the War / 09/29/66
    - University Bulletin / 12/19/66
    - University Bulletin 01/16/67
    - Vietnam Day Committee / nd
    - Vietnam Tax Protest Committee / 03/14/66 3pp
    - Vietnam Tax Protest Committee / 03/16/66
    - Vietnam Tax Protest Committee / 04/15/66 2cc
    - Witness account / Scott and Stocking docketed 12/05/66
  - File 31 (Box 4, Folder 77-79)
    - Dont Tread on Me leaflet / docketed 01/10/67
    - Academic Senate, Emergency Executive Committee / 12/27/64 4pp
    - ACLU pamphlet / November 1963
    - Ad hoc Committee on Student Conduct / nd 8pp
    - Agenda. Peace and Freedom Movement / 03/21/68
    - Alameda County McCarthy for President / nd
    - Announcement. Peace and Freedom Movement / 03/21/68
    - Anti-war leaflet / Anonymous nd
    - Appeal / Jacobson 12/21/64
    - ASUC / docketed 12/04/69
    - Bay Area Progressive Labor Movement / nd 2cc
    - Berkeley Daily Gazette. Reprint / 12/14/64
    - Berkeley Faculty Alliance. AFT Local 1474 / docketed 01/20/69
    - Bulletin of International Socialism / 12/21/64 8pp
    - Call to meeting / docketed 01/20/69
    - Call to meeting. Who are the Weathermen / docketed 12/08/69
    - Campus CORE / nd 2pp
    - Campus SDS / docketed 01/28/69
    - Campus SDS 01/24/69 2cc
    - Campus VDC / docketed 02/02/67
    - Coalition Against Tuition / docketed 12/04/69
    - Coalition for Tuition Free Higher Education / docketed 12/04/69
    - Coalition to Defend Affirmative Action By Any Means Necessary / 10/21/99
    - Committee for Justice in Civil Rights Cases / 07/18/64 10pp
    - Committee on Academic Freedom / 12/29/64 7pp
    - Community for a New Politics / November 1968
    - Conservatives for Political Action / nd
    - Coordinating Committee of the S.F. Peace and Freedom Party 03/03/68
    - Draft statement / UC faculty members / nd
    - Editorial. Reprint / Hutchins 12/20/64
    - Free Speech Movement Newsletter / 10/20/64
    - Free Speech Movement Newsletter / 11/10/64
    - Funds for Justice / nd
    - Independent Socialist Club / 01/24/69
    - Independent Socialist Club / nd
    - Invitation to community protest / docketed 01/24/69
    - Labor Party Caucus / nd
    - Leaflet / Steinberg docketed 12/04/69
    - Leaflet / Blitman docketed 12/01/69
    - Leaflet for a film screening / docketed 10/10/67
    - Leaflet in support of Spider magazine / 03/24/65
    - Leaflet. Call to debate. / docketed 04/10/67
    - Leaflet. RSU 01/22/69
    - Leaflet. RSU 01/31/69
    - Leaflet/ Stop the Draft Week / docketed 10/05/67
    - Letter / Abrams 11/23/64
    - Letter / Matson 01/29/69
    - Letter / Muscatine 12/14/64 2cc
    - Letter / Rowe 12/08/64
    - Letters. / Henry May 12/16/64
    - Memo / Chamberlain 12/06/64 2cc
    - Memo / Henry May 12/03/64
    - Memo / Kornhauser 12/02/64
    - Motion. Academic Senate / 12/05/66
    - Non-violent Park Supporters / docketed 05/28/69
    - Northern California McCarthy for President Campaign / 03/23/68
    - Notice. Consumers Co-op of Berkeley / docketed 05/29/69
    - Office of the Chancellor / Kerr 12/23/64 2pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Strong 10/26/64 10pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Strong 11/24/64
    - Open letter / Ham nd
    - Pamphlet. Faculty members of UC Berkeley / nd
    - Pamphlet. The Regents / Garson 1965
    - Pamphlet. University of Wisconsin / nd
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. Minutes of a Black Panther meeting / 03/03/67
    - Peace and Freedom Party / 04/07/68
    - Petition to stop the war / nd 9cc
    - Platform. Independent Socialists Club / 03/05/68
    - Platform. Independent Socialists Club / 03/05/68 2pp
    - Platform. Peace and Freedom Movement / nd
    - Poster. Berkeley Gallery / nd
    - Proposal. Committee on Academic Freedom / 12/08/64 8pp
    - Report / Rossman and Hollander 1964
    - Report. Graduate Fact-Finding Committee / 12/13/64 23pp 2cc
    - Report. NAACP Legal Defense Fund / October 1964
    - RSU Labor Committee 12/01/69
    - Science. Reprint / 07/23/65
    - Spark newspaper / 02/20/65
    - Stamler Legal Aid Fund / 09/08/66
    - Standing order. Academic Senate / 07/15/94 2pp
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 01/23/69
    - Strike Support Committee 01/24/69
    - Student Power Workshop / Clavir 03/16/68
    - Text of Judge Kroningers decision / 12/22/64
    - The New World. Reprint / 06/29/44
    - The New York Times. Reprint 07/17/64
    - Third World Faculty / docketed 02/03/69
    - Third World Liberation Front / docketed 01/2/69 2pp
    - Third World Liberation Front / docketed 01/28/69 4pp
    - TWLF and AFT Local 1570 / nd
    - U.S.L.O. Newsletter / 12/09/64
    - U.S.L.O. Newsletter / 12/14/64 2cc
    - UC Department of Anthropology / 12/04/64
    - UC Department of Geology / 12/14/64
    - UC Department of Geology and Physics / Turner 12/08/64
    - University Bulletin / 11/07/64
    - University Bulletin / 12/14/64
    - Voter Registration Committee / nd
    - Workers for Peoples Democracy / 12/01/69
    - Young Peoples Socialist League / docketed 07/24/69
  - File 32 (Box 4, Folder 80-82)
    - Academic Senate / 01/23/67 2pp
    - Academic Senate. Notice of Meeting / 02/04/71 9pp
    - AFL-CIO Local 1695 / Wilkinson 02/16/71
    - AFT Locals 1474 and 1795 / docketed 05/28/69
    - AFT-UCD Local 2023 / 02/04/71
    - American Liberation Front / 04/20/70 2cc
    - Arab Student Association / docketed 10/10/69
    - Bay Area Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case / 04/24/76
    - Bay Area Organizing Committee for Draft Resistance / docketed 04/24/67
    - Bay Area Sparticist League / docketed 04/12/67 2cc
    - Bay Council for Soviet Jewry / docketed 10/09/69
    - Berkeley Campus International Socialists/ docketed 12/09/69
    - Berkeley SDS / 12/07/72 3pp
    - Berkeley SDS Steering Committee / 09/22/72
    - Berkeley Students for Peace / 10/03/77 2pp
    - Black Liberation Forum / docketed 04/13/70
    - Buffalo Faculty Defense Fund / 03/28/70 2cc
    - Bulletin. Office of the Chancellor / Kerley 02/23/71 2cc
    - CAC Faculty Center / 02/23/71
    - CAC Faculty Center / February 1971
    - Call to a meeting / docketed 04/22/70
    - Call to mobilize / Anonymous docketed 04/04/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee / docketed 04/14/67
    - Campus SDS / docketed 09/18/67
    - Catacombs of Berkeley / 05/01/70
    - Committee for International Womens Day / 1971
    - Committee for Student Participation / docketed 04/20/67
    - Committee of 100 / Moore April 1969
    - Committee on Liberation or Death (C.O.L.D.) / docketed 10/22/69
    - Committee to Abolish Prison Slavery / nd
    - Committee to Abolish Prison Slavery / nd
    - Committee to Stop ROTC / 02/06/75
    - Council of Faculty for Academic Responsibility / 02/12/71
    - CV / Moellering, Ralph L. nd
    - Department of History / ODonnell 05/15/70
    - Fundraising letter / Braverman nd
    - Fundraising letter / Chinowsky and Klein 01/15/70 2cc
    - Guidelines. Office of the Chancellor / 09/23/70
    - Instant News Service / 05/23/69
    - Instant News Service / 05/29/69
    - Intracollegiate Governmental Association 02/15/71
    - Invitation to a discussion / Bailey and Chamberlain 10/12/71
    - Invitation to a protest / 02/03/71
    - Iranian Students Association / 02/24/71
    - Iranian Students Association / Azimi 01/20/71 2pp
    - Leaflet / docketed 03/10/69
    - Leaflet. Knowledge for What? / Anonymous 04/03/70
    - Leaflet. Stop the San Quentin Railroad. / 09/15/70
    - Leaflet. Black Panther Party / docketed 12/05/69
    - Leaflet. Campus SDS / docketed 12/09/69
    - Leaflet. League of Women Voters / February 1971
    - Leaflet. SDS / docketed 11/03/69
    - Leaflet. Write-in McCarthy Campaign / 10/17/72
    - League of Women Voters / January 1971
    - Letter / Jenner 07/09/70 2pp
    - Letter of appeal / Keightley April 1973 4pp
    - Letter to Chancellor Heyns / Herbold nd
    - Letter. Hiroshima Day Committee / 07/27/70 2pp
    - Memo / Brucker 07/21/70
    - Memo / Brucker 08/10/70
    - Memo / Christensen 07/13/71
    - Memo / Kerley 02/02/72 2pp
    - Memo / Stuart 04/01/70
    - Memo. Department of History / Bisson 09/13/70
    - Memo. Department of History / Brucker 07/30/70
    - New York Magazine. Reprint of an editorial / 10/25/76
    - No. California Emergency Committee Against Racism in Boston / 01/20/75
    - Northern California Regional SDS / docketed 12/10/69
    - Office of the Academic Senate / 01/11/71 7pp
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 04/29/71
    - Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 04/29/71
    - Office of the Dean. College of Letters and Science / Knight 05/10/70 2pp
    - Office of the Dean. College of Letters and Science / Knight 05/28/69 2pp
    - Office of the Registrar / Gilliam 05/26/70
    - Peace Treaty News Vol. 1, No. 1 / 03/29/71
    - Peoples Park Negotiating Committee / docketed 05/27/69
    - Peoples Voice / docketed 09/18/67
    - Peoples Coalition / docketed 04/22/70
    - Political Rights Defense Fund / Crawford 03/30/75 2pp
    - Proposed platform. VOICE / 04/20/67
    - Radical History Caucus / 04/15/70
    - Request for Funding / Duster and Bogard nd 3pp
    - Resolution / Kelley 01/24/67
    - San Francisco Chronicle. Reprint / Gleason 08/03/65
    - Soledad Brothers Legal Committee / nd
    - Statement. Office of the Chancellor / 04/07/69
    - Statement. Office of the Vice Chancellor / 09/17/70 3pp
    - Student Mobilization Committee / docketed 04/12/67
    - The Friends of the Tri-Continental Progressive Students / docketed 04/21/67
    - The Los Angeles Times. Reprint 08/02/70
    - The New York Times and the New York Post articles. PRDF 03/19/75
    - The New York Times. Reprint of an editorial / 10/24/76
    - The People United #19 / January 1976
    - Tri-Continental Students Against the War / docketed 04/12/67
    - UC Academic Senate. Minutes of the Berkeley Division / 05/15/70
    - UC Berkeley Department of History / 05/11/70
    - UC Faculty for McGovern / 05/11/72
    - UC Nuclear Weapons Lab Conversion Project / 05/05/79
    - Universities National Anti-war Fund / Stamp 10/06/70 3pp
    - University Bulletin / 09/28/70
  - File 33 (Box 4, Folder 83-84)
    - AFL-CIO / docketed 03/08/67
    - AFT and CALM / docketed 01/30/67
    - AFT Local 1570 / docketed 01/23/67
    - AFT Local 1570 / docketed 04/07/67
    - ASUC Senate. Call to a vigil / docketed 01/24/67
    - Bay Area Spartacist League / 03/30/67
    - Bay Area Spartacist League / docketed 03/08/67
    - Build Spring Mobilization Committee / docketed 03/02/67
    - Call to a demonstration / docketed 03/06/67
    - Call to a rally. Campus SDS / 04/29/69
    - Call to a rally. Socialist Party USA and the YSA / docketed 08/20/69
    - Call to debate. Press of Dissent/ docketed 04/10/67
    - Call to mobilize / McCabe docketed 04/14/67
    - Call to rally. Independent Socialist Club / docketed 08/14/67
    - Campus Community for New Politics / docketed 01/30/67
    - Campus Community for New Politics / docketed 02/07/67
    - Campus Community for New Politics / docketed 02/20/67
    - Campus Community for New Politics / docketed 07/12/67
    - Campus Friends of AFT / docketed 02/02/67
    - Campus Friends of the AFT / docketed 02/07/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee / docketed 04/07/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee / docketed 04/11/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee/ docketed 04/04/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee/ docketed 04/13/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee/ docketed 04/14/67
    - Campus Mobilization Committee/ docketed 09/28/67
    - Campus Mobilization. Call to a meeting / docketed 04/06/67
    - Campus Mobilization. Vietnam Week / docketed 04/11/67
    - Campus Movement for a New America. / docketed 02/14/67
    - Campus Movement for a New America. / docketed 03/27/67
    - Campus Progressive Labor Party 01/23/67
    - Campus SDS / docketed 01/18/67
    - Campus SDS. Retain Ron Yank / docketed 05/06/69
    - Campus SDS. What Happened to the Panther Conference? docketed 07/22/69
    - Campus SDS. Stop the draft / docketed 10/02/67
    - Campus Vietnam Day Committee / docketed 01/31/67
    - CCS Bulletin / docketed 01/13/67
    - Cited Students Union / docketed 01/16/67
    - Cited Students Union / docketed 02/01/67
    - CNP candidates / docketed 02/20/67
    - Committee for Representation of Non-academic Employees / docketed 01/19/67
    - Committee for the Establishment of Community / docketed 01/12/67 2pp
    - Community for New Politics / 04/04/67
    - Community for New Politics / docketed 02/15/67
    - Community for New Politics / docketed 02/16/67
    - Community for New Politics / docketed 03/30/67
    - Constitution. ASUC / docketed 02/06/67
    - Faculty Peace Committee / docketed 03/30/67
    - Fall Offensive. Radical Student Union / 10/02/69
    - Free University of Berkeley / docketed 01/11/67
    - Free University of Berkeley / docketed 09/28/67
    - Independent Socialist Club / 02/23/67
    - Independent Socialist Club / docketed 01/24/67
    - Independent Socialist Club / docketed 02/14/67
    - Independent Socialist Club. Defend the Ghetto Uprisings. / docketed 08/16/67
    - Jerry Rubin for Mayor Committee / docketed 03/01/67
    - Latin American Political Prisoners Defense Committee / docketed 03/30/67
    - Leaflet. A new experiment in co-ed living / docketed 03/10/67
    - Leaflet. Black and Brown Stamps / docketed 09/20/69
    - Leaflet. Come See About Huey. / docketed 04/29/69
    - Leaflet. Defend the Park. / docketed 04/24/69
    - Leaflet. Stiles Hall Personal Exploration Group / docketed 10/02/69
    - Letter to the editor of the San Francisco Examiner / Coombs 04/17/69
    - Minority report / Freedman 01/06/67 8pp
    - News release. Pope John Union / 02/09/67
    - Newsletter. AFT Locals 1474 and 1570 / docketed 01/08/67
    - Office of the Chancellor / Sammet 04/23/69
    - Organization of Arab Students / docketed 02/21/67 3pp
    - Peace and Freedom Party / docketed 07/12/67
    - Peace Formula. International Society for Krishna Consciousness / 02/28/67 8pp
    - Remarks. Office of the Chancellor / Heyns 04/24/69 3pp
    - Report / Heyns 02/06/67 4pp
    - Report on the Angela Davis case. Academic Senate / 09/20/69
    - SDS / 08/21/69
    - SDS / docketed 02/20/67
    - SDS and Berkeley Anti-draft Union / docketed 08/10/67
    - SDS and Berkeley Anti-draft Union / docketed 08/29/67 2cc
    - Socialist Campaign Committee / docketed 03/06/67
    - Socialist Campaign Committee. Memorial for Malcolm X / docketed 02/20/67
    - Socialist Labor Party / docketed 02/16/67
    - Sparticist West. Vol. 2, No. 1 / 08/30/67
    - Stop the Draft Week / docketed 09/13/67
    - Student Committee on Agricultural Labor / 02/08/67
    - The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints / 04/12/67
    - The Resistance / docketed 08/16/67
    - The Warmth Committee / docketed 04/14/67
    - University Bulletin / 03/06/67
    - University Bulletin / 04/03/67
    - University Bulletin / 04/10/67
    - University Bulletin 01/23/67
    - University Bulletin 01/30/67
    - University Bulletin 02/06/67
    - University Bulletin 02/14/67
    - University Bulletin 02/20/67
    - University Bulletin 02/27/67
    - University Young Democrats / docketed 01/24/67
    - War Resisters League / docketed 02/16/67
    - War Resisters League / docketed 02/16/67
    - Young Peoples Socialist League / docketed 04/29/69
    - Young Peoples Socialist League / docketed 08/15/67
  - File 34 (Box 4, Folder 85-86)
    - Hey God, I Got Busted! Christian World Liberation Front / docketed 05/27/69
    - People or Quail? AFSCME 1695 and AFT 1570 / docketed 05/19/68 2cc
    - Support the Black Students. SDS and AASU / docketed 01/17/69
    - AFSCME 1695 / docketed 05/29/69
    - AFSCME 1695 / docketed 09/19/69
    - AFSCME Local 1695 / 02/25/69